

# Rani Kumari

Electronics & Telecommunication Engineer

## Personal Information

DOB: 10<sup>th</sup> January 1990 Nationality: Indian German Permanent Spouse dependent visa (Full time working visal

## **Profile**

A focused professional with 5+ **years** of experience in IT industry (Networking Support/Ui Path developer, Robotic Process Automation/Order Management/CRM).

Good at understanding the process and designing bots which is best suites the process to be automated.

Proficient in grasping new technical concepts and utilizing them in an effective manner.

## Contact Information



(+49) 152-25354284



Stollestrße 24, 01159 Dresden, Germany



Rani.ak.kumari@gmail.com Ranikumari.entc@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/ rani-kumari-aa8567166/

# **Educational Background**

Ajay Binay Institute of Technology, Cuttack, India *Sept.* 2011 – May 2015

- **❖** Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.) **Electronics & Telecommunication Engineering**
- CGPA: 7.45 (Indian Grading system)

# **Professional Experience**

#### Network Operation Associate

Accenture Solutions Private Limited, Bangalore, India, June 2018- November 2021

- Analysis of First business review and last invoice review of
- Validation of network performance of the circuits using the ETMS tool
- Auditing of circuit works on the basis of circuit's nature and maintaining a database
- Producing network configuration information and analysis of configuration request
- Configuration on various Core products
- Pulling the dump through SAP and catalyst for configuration
- Responsible for analysing, validating and quoting the customer's install base information, reviewing of the order booked and then accordingly set up the renewal service contracts in Oracle.
- Providing regular incident and change notification (planned & unplanned) to impacted lines of business and senior managers with appropriate data including business impact, application affected and relevant details regarding incident resolution.

#### Processes Associate

Capgemini, Bangalore, India, *May 2017 – May 2018* 

- Responsible for Order management, contract renewals and quoting process
- TLA renewals update in TM and Create new TLAs for New **Commodity Code**
- Country wise Rules and Surcharges creation
- Training the new hires in the team regarding the process
- Handing escalation cases and resolving those on call with onshore

#### Practitioner Operations

Concentrix Daksh Services India Private Limited, Bangalore, India, *Jan 2016 – Apr 2017* 

- Managing customer escalations and routing them to owing unit
- Analyzing the process errors of the team and sharing the feedback with all team members
- Participating in various learning programs
- Recommending the changes required in product and process to Team Leader



# Rani Kumari

# Language Proficiency

- English- Full professional proficiency
- German-Basic proficiency,
- Hindi- Native proficiency

## Other Skills

- Highly organized
- Focused and result oriented
- self-confident & Dedicated with a positive attitude
- **Creative Thinking**
- Team Player
- Work efficiently even under pressure

## **Hobbies**







Yoga & Meditation

Movies

Creative Writing

## Reference

Available upon request

Date: 02.01.2023

Rani Kumari

#### Software Skills

- Python
  - Numpy
  - Pandas
- Oracle 11i
  - IB, RQF, OKS
  - OBIEE
- Sales force **SFDC**

- **SAP**
- Catalyst

### Computer Skills

- Office Tool
  - Microsoft office (Excel, Word, PowerPoint)
  - MS Project

## Agile Skills

- - Limited working knowledge
- Confluence
  - Limited working knowledge

## Extra Curriculum

### Activity

- Participated in different cultural fest conducted in University
- Organising member of Technical fest in university

#### Other Skills

- Good Communication Skills in English
- Strong Determination, Dedication, Self-confident, focused and result oriented
- Highly organized and dedicated with a positive attitude

# Personal Interest

- Sports (Chess, Badminton),
- Reading Books,
- Watching Documentary Films,
- Interest in craft work